YASH TULSIANI

CONTACT

✓ ytulsiani3@gatech.edu

vtulsiani.com

630-217-3889

in ytulsiani

ytulsiani

SKILLS

Languages: Java, Python, Ruby, JavaScript,

C, Assembly, Bash, SQL

Technologies: Openstack, AWS, Concourse CI, Heroku, Cloud Foundry, Android Studio, Chef, Unity, Bosh Frameworks and Libraries: NodeJS, Ruby on Rails, Angular, JavaFX, OpenCV, Bootstrap

ACTIVITIES

GreyHat Infosec

Learned fundamentals of developing secure software. Used tools like Metasploit and Wireshark to learn how penetration testing is done in the field.

FouroFour Co · Visual Artist I work in creating visual content for local Atlanta brands used by them in marketing of their company and products.

Vibha · President

Helped start a Georgia Tech chapter for an organization raising funding and awareness for education for children in developing countries. Led club of 15 volunteers to host multiple successful awareness events and campaigns that raised thousands of dollars for the organization.

Tech The Halls ·

Vice President of Marketing Worked in executive board for an organization promoting inner-city education through connections. Responsible for finding innovative ways to increase mentor, student, and corporate sponsor awareness. Developed website for the club on bootstrap located at techthehalls.gtorg.gatech.edu.

Atlanta Humane Society Volunteered at a humane society in dog rehabilitation and adoption center. Took photos of the adoptions animals and managed their website with new animals.

SUMMARY

I am a 3rd year Computer Science major looking for a Summer 2018 and Fall 2018 internship in a software development role.

EDUCATION

Georgia Institute of Technology (Georgia Tech)

B.S. Computer Science

August 2015 - December 2018

Concentration in Information Internetworks, Artificial Intelligence, and Media

Undergraduate Research related to analyzing bus data for Georgia Tech

EMPLOYMENT

Ultimate Software

Weston, FL May 2017 to Aug 2017

Software Engineering Intern

- Worked a devops role for Platform as a Service team supporting Pivotal Cloud Foundry
- Developed pipelines for continuous integration and automation
- Moved Chef deployments to Bosh with Ruby and Python
- Managed virtual machines with Openstack

The Home Depot

Atlanta, GA May 2016 to Aug 2016

Software Engineering Intern

- · Developed Proof of Concept allowing for the development of an integrated backend over multiple store fronts with Javascript and Angular
- Helped decrease content deployment time from days to hours

PhD Founders

Schaumburg, IL Sep 2014 to Feb 2017

- · Started a tutoring company to provide low cost tutoring to over 30 students ranging from first grade to
- Managed 3 employees and developed a sustainable business plan
- · Designed phdfounders.com

Georgia Institute of Technology

Visual Content Creator

Atlanta, GA

Apr 2016 to Current

- Create content for Georgia Tech including photos, videos, and graphics using Adobe sofware
- Manage Georgia Tech's social media including Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, and Snapchat

PROJECTS

Undergraduate Research: iTrans

Implemented machine learning algorithms in Python connected to a MySQL database to predict bus arrival and departures for Georgia Tech's busing system. These algorithms will be used to provide accurate readings for the campus busing arrival estimator API.

Developed Unity application as a proof of concept for an audio centric software and hardware suite to help filmmakers focus on their work without having to micromanage their crew. Details on the project, including demo videos are available at github.com/ytulsiani/Audio-AD.

BuzzHon

Developed Game Boy Advance game in C. The game is similar to the classic game Frogger in the sense you must avoid enemies and reach to the other side before losing a certain number of lives. The code for this game is available at github.com/ytulsiani/Buzz-Hop.

Developed a Facebook Messenger bot that allows a user to discover new poetry. Used NodeJS and Python to build this and hosted it on Heroku. You can message the bot at m.me/poetryfinder and the code is available at github.com/ytulsiani/Poem-Dispenser.

MauledBy

Developed website to raise money for the ACLU that generates gifs with an image uploaded by the user. Software used to build this includes NodeJS, Python, and OpenCV. Website is live at mauledbytrump.com and the code is available at github.com/ytulsiani/Trump-WWE.